laughteryoga.org 2006-06-28

# Privacy Policy

The Dr. Kataria School Of Laughter Yoga is committed to protecting the privacy of its users and using their information responsibly. Please read below for detailed information about our privacy policy. 

**How We Use User Information**  
Our site uses a registration form to request information (email address, email type preference, country and zip code) in order to subscribe to receive our free LAFF e-newsletter. The Dr. Kataria School Of Laughter Yoga will not share your personal information with any third party without your express consent. We also request additional demographic information (gender, birthdate), which is optional. We use this information to create a better user experience. Additionally, we may share this demographic information (including country and zip code) with others including potential advertisers in an anonymous report. This demographic information will presented in a purely anonymous, aggregated manner that has no personal information attached to it. All information provided in the Email This To A Friend utility is used solely for purposes of generating one-time private emails that are sent under your email address to those parties you have designated, and no information will be stored or shared with any third party. You may, from time to time, receive information from us about new features, new services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. You may opt out of receiving future mailings from The Dr. Kataria School Of Laughter Yoga by unsubscribing.

**How Your Information is Stored**  
All personal information is stored on restricted database servers. We use industry standard measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of your information once it is in our care.

**Links To Other Sites**  
The Dr. Kataria School Of Laughter Yoga may link to other sites in context of articles or other forms. The Dr. Kataria School Of Laughter Yoga is not responsible for the content or technology that is featured or used by those sites, nor is The Dr. Kataria School Of Laughter Yoga responsible for evaluating if their privacy policy is in line with ours. Please review those sites privacy policies to determine their individual policies.

**Your Agreement**  
By using the The Dr. Kataria School Of Laughter Yoga site, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this privacy policy. We may from time to time update this policy. We will post any changes to our policy on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, you can [contact us](mailto:webmaster@laughteryoga.org).
